http://www.hps.org/privacy.html

Sections
All Sections (listing)
Chapters
All Chapters (listing)
Committees
All Committees (listing)
Journal Online
HP News (Digest)
Newsletter Highlights Archive
Operational Radiation Safety (ORS)
Privacy Statement
The Health Physics Society (HPS) is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. We have structured our websites so that, in general, you can visit us on the Web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information.
This Privacy Policy sets forth the HPS's practices regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of information that you may provide through this site. Please read this entire Privacy Policy before using this site or submitting information to HPS through this site.
By using this site and whenever you submit information through this site to HPS, you agree with the terms of HPS's Privacy Policy written below.
Data Collection
HPS only collects personally identifiable data such as your name, address, telephone number, or email address when you voluntarily submit it to HPS. This information may be used by personnel of HPS as a means to contact you to obtain more information, to improve this site, or to provide you with information that you have requested or that HPS believes may be of interest to you. Data the HPS collects will not be transferred to a third party outside of HPS without your prior consent, but it may be used within HPS or by a company acting as an agent of HPS for processing and mailing purposes. HPS may also use this information for performing marketing studies or for other commercial purposes for which it may receive compensation.
As part of the order process, if we collect credit/debit card information, your information will be used to fill your order, but we will never share your personal payment information with third parties.
While HPS makes every reasonable effort to protect the information collected through its websites, please be aware that there is always some risk involved when submitting data over the Internet. We cannot guarantee that our website is 100 percent safe from illegal tampering or "hacking." Any data transmitted over the Internet may be at risk; however, once it is received at HPS, it has the same protection that HPS extends to its own confidential information.
We track the total number of visitors to our website, the number of visitors to each page of the website, and the domain names of our visitors' Internet service providers. No personally identifiable information is gathered in this process.
Updating Your Information
If at any time you wish to stop receiving emails or other communications from us, or if you have submitted personally identifiable information through our website and would like to have that information deleted from our records, please notify us at hps@burkinc.com. You may also request access to personal data about you that HPS holds and you may have the opportunity to request a correction or amendment to your personal data.
Links to Third-Party Sites
As a convenience to our visitors, our sites may contain links to other (non-HPS) sites that we believe may offer useful information. The Privacy Policy presented here does not apply to those sites. You should contact these sites directly for information on their privacy policies, confidentiality agreements, and data collection/distribution procedures.
Children's Policy
Our website is not intended or designed to attract children under the age of 18. We do not collect personal information from any person we actually know is under the age of 18.
Cookies
Some of our websites use a technology called "non-persistent cookies," which is a small data file that a server gives to your browser when you access a website in order to let you access the pages you request and to track the pages visited. Using non-persistent cookies to track page visits helps us analyze our site usage more accurately. In cases in which non-persistent cookies are used, we will not collect personally identifiable information except with your explicit permission. Please note that linked non-HPS sites may also use cookies. HPS cannot control the use of cookies by these non-HPS sites. We also want you to know that when you link from a HPS website to another website, that site may have the ability to recognize that you have come from an HPS site. If you do not want any other websites to know that you have been on this website, we recommend that you do not use the links provided in our site.
Refunds
Refunds are not issued for purchase of The Health Physics Society memberships. Membership is canceled when the membership term expires or if an individual or institution requests that the membership be terminated.
Privacy Policy Updates
Any changes to The Health Physics Internet Privacy Policy will be posted on this page. This Privacy Policy was last updated: 21 April 2010.
